(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-pro-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
声出し応援OKです
Cheering loudly is OK.
二次販売グッズ
2nd Round Merchandise Sales
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
声出し応援OKです
Cheering loudly is OK.
二次販売グッズ
2nd Round Merchandise Sales
常闇トワ JACK!
Tokoyami Towa JACK!
あ、こっちこっち！
Ah, over here, over here!
今日は二人じゃないんすね？
It's not just the two of us today?
え？二人？
Eh? Two?
さっきの…ここで会った人たち。
The people... we met here earlier.
え？
Eh?
心で…！
With our hearts...!
Joyしてこうぜ！
Let's Joy!
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
声出し応援OKです
Cheering loudly is OK.
Tokoyami Towa 2nd Live *SHINier*
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください
Please be aware of flashing lights due to production effects.
声出し応援OKです
Cheering out loud is allowed!
二次販売グッズ 受注販売期間
2nd Round Merch Sales: Made-to-Order Period
ブレスレットライト ¥1,870
Bracelet Light - ¥1,870
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください
Please be aware of flashing lights...
...during the performance.
声出し応援OKです
Cheering loudly is OK.
Tokoyami Towa 2nd Live "SHINier" 二次販売グッズ
Tokoyami Towa 2nd Live 'SHINier'...
...Secondary Goods Sale.
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
声出し応援OKです
Cheering loudly is OK.
二次販売グッズ
Second Round Merchandise Sales
NEW ブレスレットライト
NEW: Bracelet Light
Attention ご来場のお客様へ: 演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください。声出し応援OKです。
Attention Guests: Please be aware of flashing lights due to production effects. Loud cheering is allowed!
二次販売グッズ
2nd Round Merchandise Sales
見える？この目の涙
Can you see the tears in these eyes?
命の色に滲んでいる
They are blurring into the color of life.
何を残して与えた？
What did I leave behind, what did I give?
問いかけて
Asking questions...
潰れて
...and being crushed.
青と赤と白混ざる
Blue, red, and white mix together,
この世の中で叫んでいる
screaming in the midst of this world.
何を求めて歩いた？
What was I seeking as I walked?
追いかけて
Chasing after...
疲れて
...and getting tired.
どのくらい以上？
How much longer?
壊れているの？
Is it broken?
壊れているよ
It is broken.
それでも息をしたい
Even so, I want to breathe.
したい
I want to.
君に見えてるの？
Can you see it?
夢のように最後の
Just like a dream, my final...
言葉も詰まるよ
...words get stuck.
ERROR
遠い日のこと
From distant days...
淡い光が空に溢れている
...a pale light overflows into the sky.
何を選んで並べた？
What did I choose to line up?
涙色重ねて
Layering the colors of tears.
浮かぶその体
That floating body...
意識の中溶けて滲んでしまう
...melts and blurs within my consciousness.
何を見てきて比べた？
What have I seen and compared?
悲しくて
Feeling sad...
忘れて
...and forgetting.
どのくらい以上？
How much longer?
歪んでいるの？
Is it distorted?
歪んでいるよ
It is distorted.
それでも息をしたい
Even so, I want to breathe.
したい
I want to.
夢を見ているの？
Am I dreaming?
想う君に最後の
To you whom I think of, my final...
言葉も詰まるよ
...words get stuck.
ERROR
与えることも 失うことも
Giving and losing,
忘れることも できないの
I can't even forget them.
暴れだす このエラーコード
This error code runs wild.
壊して笑う 僕がまた
I break it and laugh again.
壊しているの
I am breaking it.
壊して知るの
I break it and learn.
それでも涙
Even so, the tears,
痛い 痛い
they hurt, they hurt.
君に届いたの
Did it reach you?
歌う声に 最期の
In my singing voice, the final...
言葉 並べても
...words, even if I line them up,
重なる色 滲んで
the overlapping colors blur.
壊れているの
It is breaking.
壊れているよ
It is breaking apart.
それでも息を
Even so, I want...
したい したい
...to breathe, to breathe.
君に見えてたの
Could you see it?
夢のように 最期の
Like a dream, the final...
言葉 つまるよ
...words get stuck.
乾いた
A parched...
虚しさと
...emptiness and
小さなこの空を
this small sky...
塞いだ あなたの色
...were blocked by your color.
手を伸ばすほどに 痛むの
It hurts the more I reach out.
僕たちは 何度も 何度も
We ask, again and again,
問いかけて
asking questions.
灯火は 迷子を 照らすかな
Will the lamp light the way for the lost?
まだ 世界は 目を 閉じたまま
The world still keeps its eyes closed,
やがて 消えていくの
and eventually, it will fade away.
静かな
A quiet...
暗闇と
...darkness and
確かな 感覚を
a certain sensation.
君の中の正義が
If the justice inside you...
愛が こぼれ落ちたら
...if the love spills over,
全て 試されてる
it feels like...
みたいで
...everything is being tested.
伝えていたいもの
What I want to convey,
何度も 失って
I lose it again and again.
この日々が 夢であるなら
If these days are just a dream,
まだ 心は 目を 閉じたまま
my heart still keeps its eyes closed,
やがて 消えて 崩れて
eventually disappearing, crumbling away...
いく
...completely.
やめてよ
Stop it.
震える感情を
Kill these trembling...
殺して
...emotions.
僕たちは 過ちの中で
We are tested, amidst our mistakes,
何度も 試されて
again and again.
まだ 正義や 愛とか 言うけど
Though we still speak of justice and love,
この世界は 目を 閉じたまま
this world still keeps its eyes closed,
やがて 消えて 崩れて
eventually disappearing, crumbling away...
いく
...completely.
風に吹かれて
Blown by the wind,
誰も気付かぬよう
so that no one notices,
区別がつかない
indistinguishable,
モノクロの世界
in a monochrome world.
まるで 私は 息を止めていた
It was as if I was holding my breath.
無為よ 遠くても 叶えたい 私は
Even if it's meaningless and far away, I want to make it come true.
広大な世界 想いも 抱きしめていたいのに
I wanted to embrace this vast world and my feelings, but...
夢のキャンバスに 描き続ける意味は
The meaning of continuing to paint on the canvas of my dreams,
この胸に 輝いている それ...
Is shining right here in my heart...
笑えることに 意味などないけど
There's no meaning in being able to laugh, but...
拾い集めた カケラ 失うの
Will I lose the fragments I gathered?
そして夜は その冷たさを
And the night melted away that coldness,
溶かして 手を伸ばした
And I reached out my hand.
無為の日よ 遠くても 届けたい 私は
Even on meaningless days, far away, I want to reach you.
受け止めてく 涙も 抱きしめていたいのに
I want to accept and embrace even the tears, but...
夢のキャンバスに 心込めるのは
Putting my heart into the canvas of my dreams,
この空に 描き出してく それ...
I'll keep sketching it out into this sky...
そして夜は その冷たさを
And the night melted away that coldness,
溶かして 手を伸ばした
And I reached out my hand.
無為の日々 遠くても 叶えたい 私の
Even through meaningless days, far away, I want to grant my...
広大な世界 想いも 言葉で包んだ
I wrapped this vast world and my feelings in words.
夢のキャンバスに 色を足していく
Adding colors to the canvas of my dreams,
この胸に 今 輝いて
Shining in my heart right now.
強くなくてもいい
It's okay not to be strong.
壊れかけてもいい
It's okay to be on the verge of breaking.
この心は 常(とわ)に羽ばたいて
This heart will flap its wings forever (Towa-ni),
響くように 塗り替えていく
Repainting it so it resonates.
Palette
みんな！
Everyone!
こんやっぴー！トワ様です！
Konyappi! It's Towa-sama!
あ、こんやっぴーって返してくれるんだ
Oh, you're returning the 'Konyappi'!
いぇーい！
Yay!
常闇トワ 2nd Live 「SHINier」
Tokoyami Towa 2nd Live 'SHINier'
いよいよ始まりましたー！
Has finally started!
えー ちょっとびっくりすると思うんですけども
Um, I think you might be surprised,
最初に「Error」を歌わせていただきました
But I sang 'Error' first.
びっくりした人？
Who was surprised?
そうだよね そうだよね びっくりしますよね
Yeah, right? Right? You'd be surprised.
で そのあとに「Twilight」と「Palette」を歌わせていただきました
And after that, I sang 'Twilight' and 'Palette'.
やっぱね 「Error」を持ってきた理由なんですけれども
The reason I brought 'Error' into the setlist is,
やっぱね まああの「Error」を聴いて常闇トワのことを知ってくれた みたいな人がやっぱ多いと思うんだよね
I think there are many people who got to know Tokoyami Towa after listening to 'Error'.
そうだよね？
Right?
そう 多いから なんかちょっとエモいの持ってこようかなみたいな感じで
Since there are many, I thought I'd bring something emotional.
もうそんな感じで コロっとサラっと決めちゃいました
So, I decided on it just like that, quite simply.
なんか結構最初の方に こうしっとりする曲を持ってきたのは
Bringing such mellow songs to the beginning part,
結構挑戦的だったのかなと思うんですけども
Was probably quite a challenge, I think.
どうでした？
How was it?
ありがとう
Thank you.
えー みんなTシャツ着てくれてるやん！
Eh, everyone is wearing the T-shirt!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
ペンライトはね あの 鈍器にもなりかねないので気をつけてください
Be careful with the penlights, they could become blunt weapons.
可愛いんだけど 可愛いのにね
They're cute, though. Even though they're cute.
まあ、そうそう、それもありますけども、
Well, yeah, there is that too, but...
思い出として残してください。
please keep it as a memory.
はい。
Yes.
そしてね、今回、えー、ライブなんですけれども、
And, um, regarding the live concert this time,
セカンドアルバムが、えー「深」というアルバムになっておりまして、
since my second album is titled "Shin" (Depth/True),
まあライブもね、その「深」に沿って、
the live is also based on that "Shin",
えー、「SHINier」という風に付けさせて... いただいてます。
and I was allowed to name it "SHINier".
あの歌はいいけど喋りが下手っていう
My singing is fine but my talking is bad,
致命的に下手なんだけど大丈夫そうか？
like fatally bad, but is that okay with you guys?
あ、ありがとうございます、ありがとうございます。
Ah, thank you, thank you.
えー、このね、「SHINier」はね、えー、光るとか輝くっていう意味があるので、
Um, this "SHINier" has the meaning of to shine or sparkle, so,
今日のね、ライブは来てくれてるみんなの心を
for today's live, for the hearts of everyone who came,
輝かせるような
I want to make it a live
ライブにしてきたと思います！
that makes you all shine!
えー、セカンドアルバムのね、楽曲もいっぱいあるのでお楽しみにしといてください。
Um, there are many songs from the second album too, so please look forward to it.
ありがとう。
Thank you.
アルバムも買ってくれましたか？
Did you buy the album too?
ありがとう。嬉しいです。
Thank you. I'm happy.
なんか今日もちょっとライブ前にあのエゴサしてたんですけども、
Like, today too, just before the live, I was ego-searching a bit,
あのいっぱい現地でも買いましたみたいなポスカ... ポストカード？
and saw "I bought a lot at the venue"... posca... postcards?
ゲットしましたみたいな感じで
Like "I got them!",
つい... ポストしてるのを見て、あ、ポストしてるのを見て、すごい嬉しかったです。
seeing people twee... posting that, ah, seeing people post that, made me very happy.
まだ慣れないんだよね。
I still can't get used to it, huh.
うん。
Yeah.
えー、そして、今日なんですけれども、ファーストと一緒で生バンドでやっております！
Um, and, for today, just like the First Live, we are performing with a live band!
イェーイ！かっこよかったでしょ？
Yay! They were cool, right?
もう最初だけじゃないから、これからずっとかっこいいのを演奏してくれます。
It's not just the beginning, they'll keep playing cool stuff from now on.
よろしくお願いいたします。
Please give them a hand.
はい。
Yes.
えー、今日しか... なんと！今日しか聴けないライブアレンジがあるかもなんで、
Um, only today... surprisingly! There might be live arrangements you can only hear today, so,
楽しんで、盛り上がってくれたら嬉しいです。
I'd be happy if you enjoy it and get hype.
はい。
Yes.
そして、今日は現地だけじゃなくて、配信もしております！
And, today is not just at the venue, we are also streaming!
なんと、ここら辺に手を振ると可愛いトワちゃんが、あの、インターネット...
Surprisingly, if I wave my hand around here, the cute Towa-chan will... um... the internet...
あ、ありがとうございます、ありがとうございます。
Ah, thank you, thank you.
はいはい、あまりそんなあの、言われ慣れてないもんで。
Yes yes, I'm not really used to being told that.
はい。
Yes.
えー、なんかいろんなとこにアピールしながらやってこうかなと思っております。
Um, I'm thinking of doing this while appealing to various places.
えー、そして、今回のハッシュタグなんですけれども、ライブの感想ハッシュタグ、
Um, and, regarding the hashtag this time, the live impression hashtag,
えー、シャープ常闇トワセカンドでたくさんポストしてください！
please post a lot with the hashtag #TokoyamiTowa2nd!
スクリーンショットOKっていうことなのでいっぱい、あのちょっといい...
Since screenshots are okay, please take lots... um, ones that are good...
あの盛れてる感じのでお願いいたします。スクリーンショットして、あの投稿する場合は。
ones where I look cute. Please, if you screenshot and post.
はい、お願いいたします。
Yes, please.
そして！なんと...
And! Surprisingly...
あ...
Ah...
これいつもの流れだから分かっちゃうかもしれないけど、えー...
This is the usual flow so you might already know, but, um...
そうなんです。えー、YouTubeとTikTokでご覧の方は、あー、ここまでとなっております。
That's right. For those watching on YouTube and TikTok, ah, this is where it ends.
すみません。
I'm sorry.
えー？！お前ら「えー」じゃないだろ！いるだろ！
Eeh?! You guys aren't "Eeh"! You're here!
何が「えー」なんだよ。何に対しての「えー」なんだよ。
What is "Eeh"? What are you "Eeh"-ing at?
ね、あの配信の見てくれてる人が「えー」っていう、あ、代弁してくれたってことね？
Hey, the people watching the stream said "Eeh", ah, so you spoke for them, right?
そうだよねそれね。
That's right, isn't it.
はい。
Yes.
なのでね、えー、まだまだ一緒に盛り上がりたいみんなは！概要欄から配信サイトを
So, um, everyone who still wants to get hype together! Check the streaming site in the description,
チェックして購入してくださいね！
and please purchase it!
はーい。
Yeeees.
ということで...
With that being said...
次の曲...
The next song...
行こうかなと思うんですけども...
I'm thinking of moving on to it, but...
えー、まずちょっとアンケートを取りたいと思います。
Um, first I want to take a little survey.
えー本日、えー東京から来たよって方！
Um today, um those who came from Tokyo!
半分ぐらいかな？半分ぐらい。
About half? About half.
えー、じゃあ東京じゃないとこから来た人！
Um, then people who came from places other than Tokyo!
無茶苦茶多いやん、めちゃありがとうやん。
There's a ton of you, thank you so much.
えー、じゃあ... じゃあ北海道から来た人！
Um, then... Then people who came from Hokkaido!
いるやん！
There are some!
マジかよ、ありがとう。
Seriously? Thank you.
じゃあ沖縄から来たって人！
Then people who say they came from Okinawa!
お、いるいるいるいるいるいる！ありがとうありがとう。ありがとう。
Oh there are, there are! Thank you, thank you. Thank you.
えーじゃあ、ちょっとあのもっと拡大していいですか？
Um then, can I expand it a bit more?
えー... 日本じゃないとこから来た人！
Um... People who came from outside Japan!
おいおい、めちゃめちゃいるじゃねーか。
Oi oi, there are tons of you.
おお、すごいすごい。ありがとう。
Oh, amazing amazing. Thank you.
えーじゃあ、さらに無茶苦茶絞って、
Um then, narrowing it down ridiculously further,
えー... じゃあ飛行機を...
Um... then people who [missed] their flight...
え？
Eh?
いるやん！
You guys are here!
え？すごい。
Wow, amazing.
ありがとうございます、ありがとうございます。
Thank you, thank you.
ということで… なんか「わー」って今 言えました？
So... were you able to say 'waa' just now?
まだでも足りないか。
Maybe it's still not enough, though.
じゃあトワ… 掛け声しちゃおうかな？
Then maybe Towa... should do a call-and-response?
盛り上がれますか！？
Can you get hyped!?
結構最初なのに声出てるやん。
You're actually pretty loud even though it's the start.
なんか何回かやろうかなって思ってたけど、
I was thinking of doing this a few times, but...
結構声出てたけど…
...since you were pretty loud...
ちょ、もう一回やっていいか、じゃあ。
Let me do it one more time, then.
盛り上がれますか！？
Can you get hyped!?
うおおお！
Whoa!
じゃあ、次の曲いくぞ！
Alright, let's go to the next song!
有明ー！
Ariake!
いくぞ有明！
Let's go, Ariake!
無料パートは終了いたしました。ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching!
無料パートは終了いたしました。
The sneak peek part of the show has ended.
ご視聴ありがとうございました！
Thank you for watching!